<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2018-08-09T03:41:40+00:00</updated><id>/en/</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: AI and master</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: AI and master" /><published>2018-07-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/">&lt;p&gt;The typhoon has just passed, bringing abundant rainfall. This is the blessing of Taiwan, and there is no shortage of water in summer; however, in recent years, stable water supply has always been a challenge for Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚰 You may not know that more than half of the water pipes in Taiwan are still plastic water pipes used to popularize tap water 30 years ago. These plastic pipes are limited to funds and cannot be completely replaced. As a result, the water leakage rate of the entire pipe is as high as 15%, and the water lost by the pipeline is nearly 1 billion tons per year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a big question, is there a solution? There are indeed experts who are doing “grab the leak”. Taishui’s existing 80 masters carry a “leak detector” that can amplify 900 times of sound, and “listen” back and forth in the sewer. The seniors have 30 years of experience. However, 80 of them go down one by one, and they can circle around Taiwan in three years. Even if they are not sleepy, it is difficult to find new leaks in real time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This hot problem, I didn’t expect to see the dawn of an AI technology recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning, I was in the President’s Cup hackathon. For the first time, I saw the proposal of the “Rescue Water Baby” team and found that they used the technology of “supervised learning”, which means that the trapped masters told the machine. What kind of data is heard indicates that there is a leak, and then the “deep learning” algorithm is used to predict whether the field check is correct. By the time the “machine apprentice” gradually builds the model, it can save the masters a lot of time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🕚 Such a system is not the first invention in Taiwan, but also a solution for Israeli company developers, but it is costly. In Taiwan, the system written in open source has reached 70% accuracy, and the time it takes to find a leak source has dropped to one-tenth of the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;自主 Self-developed technology has one advantage: it can be used in other fields, such as smart meters or natural gas pipelines. Because of the pressure and flow rate, this concept can also be used. The “Rescue Water Baby” team will also represent Taiwan in the next month to participate in the acceleration plan organized by the New Zealand government to provide solutions to local water leakage problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the interesting thing about this case is that there is always a voice in the workshop: AI is coming, and human work opportunities will be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👴 For example, the 80 masters who caught the leak, are they unemployed when AI comes? completely opposite! The process of machine learning will continue to require the wisdom of human beings to “fill in” and constantly let people learn from each other in order to solve the problem one by one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 “Rescue Water Baby” incorporates the wisdom of the master, solves the problem in collaboration, and finds new value for people. This is what we expect.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會創新" /><summary type="html">&quot;Rescue the baby&quot; incorporates the wisdom of the master, solves the problem in collaboration, and finds new value in the value of people. This is what we expect.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bf74b4534e016990033a3a484b8cd79f12eb4fab.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week Column: Revelation of Hibiscus</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week Column: Revelation of Hibiscus" /><published>2018-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%e9%a6%ac%e5%a4%aa%e9%9e%8d%e9%83%a8%e8%90%bd&quot;&gt;马太鞍&lt;/a&gt; is the largest tribe of the ami and one of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/sub/travelspot/eastern/index.php?id=33&quot;&gt;youth travel points&lt;/a&gt; planned by the youth department in hualien. in the past, the mountains and valleys were all &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#fata'an&quot;&gt;fata’an&lt;/a&gt;, and the “Matai Saddle” was transliterated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of last month, I went to the Mata Ang tribe to meet and met &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapulong.com/&quot;&gt;Mablon Farm&lt;/a&gt;. master ulang (kechunyu) tells us about the farm when it is always a whisper, so that everyone laughs. Four years ago, she started her own business from the land of her home. Today, the Mabulon Farm is open to popularity by relying on a large number of quality organic wild vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to crops, Mablon Farm has also gained community friendship. Ulang invites the tribes to work together, become mutual farming partners, and more often care for their neighbors: “When I see people who need help, I will drive them and often help me see the medicines and read the official documents,” she said. &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#:mapolong&quot;&gt;Mapulong&lt;/a&gt; In the language, it means “together”. Ulang does make the farm a bridge in the tribe through action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 How do tribal youths find links to tribes? Lamen (CaiYijing), chairman of the Mata Sang Tribe Eco-Cultural Industry Development Association, is very impressed. More than a decade ago, Lamen, who graduated from the sect, returned to the tribe. From the study of the Taiwan Science and Technology Program at the time, he helped to plan a series of experiences. Mablon Farm is one of the agricultural experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💪 Lamen believes that although this series of projects is small, the benefits are beyond imagination - in addition to making more people aware of the tribal culture, the various ethnic groups in the eastern region are also promoting the way through promotion. , to establish a closer relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💯 [太巴塱] with Matthew Saddle (https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%A4%AA%E5%B7%B4%E5%A1%B1%E9%83%A8%E8%90%BD)(Tafalong) tribe, also started from more than ten years ago &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/sub/travelspot/eastern/services.php?pid=57&amp;amp;id=225&quot;&gt;participation plan&lt;/a&gt;. how to get young friends to come to the tribe to gain in-depth experience is the subject of katai (xiaomingshan), the chief executive of the taiba village community building association, and the brainstorming of the tribes. for this reason, they even have only the annual sacrifices that the tribes participated in &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/eventscontent.php?id=498&amp;amp;securechk=8cca1365ab64f567b55bc04a26c84c14&quot;&gt;open to the public&lt;/a&gt;. These efforts have enabled the Taipa tribe to carry out the grand travel plan to date, with an average satisfaction rate of 99.8 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌿 This reminds me of the bitterness of the greens in the soup when I ate. It didn’t take long for me to taste the sweetness. The tribe’s friend said that this is a common local wild vegetable &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#sokoy&quot;&gt;sokoy&lt;/a&gt; (hibiscus,xiuguamilanguagepinyin). The same is true of the stories of Ulang, Lamen, and Kanew: the hard work ahead will eventually return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have time, you may wish to take a trip and taste the taste of hibiscus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">The same is true of the stories of Ulang, Lamen, and Kanew: the hard work ahead will eventually return.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b3847c96045edae82bc127c07d93ade99863b151.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Local partners to create an Asian future</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Local partners to create an Asian future" /><published>2018-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/">&lt;p&gt;🌏 At the beginning of May, I went to Taichung to participate in the Asia-Pacific Social Enterprise Summit of Tomorrow Asia with more than 30 international speakers from 15 countries. This event, which was hosted by the Social Enterprise, the Magpie Foundation, and the Eli International, attracted thousands of people, let me see the connection between Taiwan and the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🐟 Inside and outside the venue, more than 30 sessions and more than 60 booths have made me different and amazing. One of the most impressive is the conversation with Gavin Armstrong, founder of Lucky Little Ironfish. Before the meeting, when I asked Gavin for a personal profile, he did not talk about himself, and completely focused on the seriousness of the iron deficiency problem in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attitude is also reflected in the operation of Lucky Little Ironfish, which is to brainstorm with the people and find local solutions – such as the “fish” they built in Cambodia, and the majority of vegetarians. India has changed to the shape of &quot;leaves&quot;. With such meticulous care, we have implemented the social innovation spirit of &quot;focusing on social issues, inspiring innovation through innovation, and leading innovation through innovation&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same feelings come from the team of &quot;Pears want to live&quot; in Taichung. They combine design, small farmers and other social enterprise partners to transform the pear stems of high pears into unique ones. Think of the pen, solve the problem of air pollution caused by burning pear stems. The social enterprise market has stringped up the local agriculture, crafts, cultural and creative ecosystems, so that friends from all over the world can see the thickness of life and social connections in Taiwan. In addition, this summit successfully enabled the speakers from all walks of life to come up with social issues such as silver hair, food and agriculture, environmental green energy, and weak employment. They not only shared how social innovation can change their lives, but also participate. The examples are presented from a complementary perspective. This kind of discussion makes the issue more stereoscopic, and it also encourages those who participate to understand how to combine multiple forces and respond to the concept of “cross-sector partnership” (SDG 17.17) in the sustainable development goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in a cross-departmental discussion, I proposed the analogy: government agencies are like NPOs (non-profit organizations). One of our missions is to recognize friends who solve social problems together and help solve problems for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌄 As Vice President Chen Jianren said in his speech, the government is working with the community to plan a &quot;social innovation action plan&quot; for the next few years. It is expected that through &quot;value cultivation, capital acquisition, innovation, regulation, and regulation, Strategies such as promoting expansion and international links, continue to integrate resources across ministries, assist friends who are interested in innovation, and find common solutions to social problems. And I am very happy to be one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/QtykZeZRe88&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷、魏守斌、薛雅婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">One of our missions is to recognize friends who solve social problems together and help solve problems for everyone.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/08b38a4651ca9cf8163529894a98ad0627de97f5.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Is the Suhua Reformation the safe way for locomotives to go home? Collaborative meeting site observation</title><link href="/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is the Suhua Reformation the safe way for locomotives to go home? Collaborative meeting site observation" /><published>2018-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F/">&lt;p&gt;On April 27, 2018, the PDIS Group's Total Social Innovation Center held a thirty-second collaborative meeting to discuss the issue of multi-vehicle traffic passing through the Suhua reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;suhua-changed-unplanned-traffic-locomotive-controversy&quot;&gt;Suhua changed unplanned traffic locomotive controversy&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suhua changed its name to the 9th line Suhua Highway mountain road improvement plan, started planning in 2009, started construction in 2011, On February 5, 2018, the Suao-East Australia section was completed and opened to traffic, and small cars were opened. Since Suhua Reform did not open locomotives or heavy locomotives, many locomotives protested when they opened up. They believed that the ban on locomotive traffic in Suhua was a discrimination against locomotives and caused controversy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/350438d6348a63737e45c0bee581b542f5cad01a_1_580x500.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Suhua change road section overview, the picture is taken from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://thbu4.thb.gov.tw/page?node=6861c85c-e12e-468e-b885-f3e9d29d40ed&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;understanding of Suhua&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was proposed by the user Xiu Ming on the public policy participation platform on February 5th [&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/4afaf924-a334-4d90-b580-a2183a87993c&quot;&gt;Open Suhua changed to multiple vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, after the completion of the case on february 9, the threshold of 5,000 people was crossed on march 15. after the discussion of the open government liaison meeting, it became the subject of discussion in the collaborative meeting. the core issue of the case is that taiwanese locomotives are not the same as foreigners. the ministry of communications has long planned the policy of diversion of steam locomotives. taiwan's engineering environment design targets locomotives, and the locomotive driving space has not been properly allocated, resulting in the lack of lane concept for locomotives for a long time. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iot.gov.tw/modules/publication/publication-details?node=3598166a-c839-4f0d-8beb-33c093e49de0&amp;amp;id=40b33382-06bb-4c86-9c38-2affa9c17e12&quot;&gt;motorcycle policy white paper&lt;/a&gt; By strengthening the locomotive driving education and training mechanism, or the elderly people to continue or give up the safety mechanism of using the vehicle, to strengthen the habits of the locomotive family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e24c0a6c493a601dad9bcf5a69161b898741dc37.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The vision and plan presented in the locomotive policy white paper &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;locomotive-rights-promotion-association-suhua-highway-is-more-dangerous-than-suhua&quot;&gt;Locomotive Rights Promotion Association: Suhua Highway is more dangerous than Suhua.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A second person from Hualien said that he would take 20 Suhua Highways a year, on this road. The impression is the word &quot;fear.&quot; The Locomotive Rights Promotion Association also believes that for the locomotive family, Suhua Highway has a more dangerous environment, high illegal sections, narrow roads, poor night vision, and longer driving time. In contrast, the Suhua-changed tunnel is much larger and the interior space is more spacious. It should be a safer road. The Gaogong Bureau had previously pointed out that the air and noise in the tunnel affected the body and mind of the locomotive knight, as well as the danger of mixed traffic between the locomotive and the car. Therefore, the Suhua was not allowed to change to the locomotive. The proponent believes that the current air in the tunnel does not affect the body, not to mention the 18-kilometer mountain tunnel in Japan. It is also open to locomotives. It is questioned that the Ministry of Communications has enlarged the small risks and ignored the Suhua Highway. high risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/91e7f22df03a7a0290dc1d350f79671540af15a3_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The second person explains the danger of Suhua Highway &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;department-of-transportation-vehicles-are-diverted-and-there-is-a-safe-road&quot;&gt;Department of Transportation: Vehicles are diverted, and there is a safe road&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications reports that the Suhua Highway has been used for more than 80 years. In the past, the design was actually not so much, so the road section The design is not very good. At present, the Suhua reform plan has improved the situation of the Suhua Highway. As for the Suhua Reform, it was hoped that the impact on the nearby ecological and settlements would be reduced when planning. Therefore, the two-way two-lane road was configured, and the vehicle type was also implemented in stages and diversions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications explained that in the future, Suhua will be replaced by large trucks, passing buses and small buses, and the Suhua Highway will be planned as a rest road, prohibiting the passage of large trucks, only sightseeing buses. , minibuses, locomotives and bicycles. In this way, the big trucks and locomotives that are most likely to be in a car accident will be diverted. These two roads will be safe roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the opening of the locomotive into the Suhua, due to the speed limit of the Suhua, the locomotive is more likely to cause casualties after the collision, so it is not desirable to open the tunnel where the locomotive passes through the Suhua.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications also added that if the typhoon comes and the Suhua Highway is unable to pass, it will plan an emergency response plan for the locomotive to pass the Suhua reform. At that time, the Suhua Reform Association will ban the passage of vehicles above the car. After the locomotive knights gather at a certain place, they will pass through the front and rear guides to pass the Suhua reform. In the follow-up discussion, the host team clarified the arguments agreed by both parties. Everyone hopes to reduce the chance of accidents in the tunnel. It also hopes to strengthen the habits of the locomotives and reduce the casualties of the locomotives on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the two sides still have some controversy about some figures. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that the national highway observation of the trial of heavy-duty vehicles found that the probability of violation of locomotives is higher than that of ordinary vehicles; however, the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association believes that the rate of casualties on the national highway is lower than that of ordinary roads. It is a safer choice. The Gaogong Bureau also pointed out that in the past, these roads were rarely discussed with the use of ethnic groups. However, the planning of the Suhua landscape road has already communicated with the local residents in advance, and the needs of the people will be investigated in advance in the future. planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the heavy machine can have different positions on both sides of the national road, regardless of the Ministry of Communications or the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association, it agrees that the driving concept of the locomotive lane should be promoted as much as possible to reduce the danger of locomotive driving. The discussion in the afternoon discussed how to safely pass the Suhua Highway and the Suhua Reform. After the discussion, the two groups reported the results of their respective discussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-collaboration-preliminary-research-trial-locomotive-has-a-consensus&quot;&gt;Group collaboration, preliminary research, trial locomotive has a consensus&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group began to focus on the reasons why Suhua changed to the locomotive. The Locomotive Rights Promotion Association believes that the temperature and air quality values ​​can be placed at the entrance of the Suhuahuan Tunnel to allow the locomotive riders to choose whether or not to enter. In terms of locomotive roads, more stringent regulations can be formulated to force the locomotives to Drive in a lane-like way and strictly enforce the law through the monitor. If you are concerned that the air quality is too bad, you can also plan traffic control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d47f87becdf8b00993ceb9a41dd5000b81db8074_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The first group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The General Administration of Highways believes that these packages are not enough. According to the General Administration of Highways, the Suhuahuan Tunnel has been planned to exclude locomotives from the beginning, so only one fast lane plus one emergency lane is designed. If the locomotive is to be opened, the design of the tunnel needs to be greatly adjusted, including section, lane, electromechanical, traffic control, and emergency contingency plans. The General Administration of Highways pointed out that the Yamate Tunnel in Japan has specially improved the ventilation of the tunnel in order to allow the locomotive to pass, and added water mist equipment to control the temperature inside the tunnel. In contrast, the Suhuachang tunnel is not planned to allow locomotives to pass, so air quality, temperature control, and even lanes are not suitable for locomotive traffic, because the plan does not cover the results of the locomotive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the General Administration of Highways promised that in the future, it would be possible to issue a package for the research report of the long tunnel of the locomotive, and to evaluate the feasibility of the locomotive passing the Suhua reform. These research reports can be used as reference for Taiwan's long tunnel planning in the future. As for the improvement of Suhua Highway, the discussion in the first group suggests that some sections of the road should be built with tunnels or planned for locomotive lanes. If it is really forbidden to pass large trucks in the future, it should be strictly enforced, and even buses must enter. It should also be reviewed for application. Some sections of the road should be cut and straightened, and the lighting conditions should be paid attention to, and some street lights should be added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discussion in the second group has a clear consensus on the trial locomotive traffic. It may be possible to do a trial after all the buses have been opened, so that there will be follow-up information as an assessment of whether the locomotive is open or not. In terms of the tunnel environment, it is also necessary to pre-collect relevant standards such as temperature and air quality of tunnels passing through the international locomotive. The second group of discussions also found that the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association and the Ministry of Communications were inconsistent in the “safety” standards. It is recommended that the follow-up be evaluated together for a focused discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/1bd8d1a6b2dd9e99a0bb43faa3af0e5a26a2be0b_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The second group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, I hope that such roads will be evaluated by scholars and organizations related to organic vehicles before planning. I hope that this opportunity will be used to set common standards for the open conditions of locomotives that everyone can accept. Not everyone's standards are different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After these comments have been completed, the political commissar Tang Feng will bring the &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kz3fwa0=/&quot;&gt;conference conclusion&lt;/a&gt; to the government conference to report to the Executive Dean and The heads of relevant ministries can get the results of these discussions as a follow-up policy study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz3FWa0=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VbwKBK24T_g&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;participants-are-looking-forward-to-the-establishment-of-an-early-consultation-mechanism&quot;&gt;Participants are looking forward to the establishment of an early consultation mechanism&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The congressional assistants attending the meeting said that it is very difficult to see that the executive can adopt such a form of meeting and hope that the meeting can have some concrete results. References can also be made to relevant materials. He is also very appreciative of the form of the mind map, thinking that this can see the whole picture of the issue. The official colleagues also said that the issue mental map is clearly organized, more systematic, and the context is clearer. Participants said that only the experience of public hearings had been held before. Today's collaborative meetings are somewhat different from the public hearings. The hosts are relatively neutral and hope to be used in other topics. They think that it is very good to improve the discussion environment. The public hearing will only send a letter, and I don't know if there is any positive action. Participants believe that the government should establish various consultation meetings in the spirit of collaborative meetings in the future. Listen to the voices and ideas of different people before policy planning, and also investigate different evidences. &quot;The previous consultation process should be established. Get up, otherwise this kind of controversy will be more and more.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Since Suhua Reform did not open locomotives or heavy locomotives, many locomotives protested when they opened up. They believed that the ban on locomotive traffic in Suhua was a discrimination against locomotives and caused controversy. After the discussion at the meeting, the General Administration of Highways promised to send out relevant research on the locomotive long tunnel for reference for subsequent policies. In the future, before planning, such roads also hope that scholars and organizations related to organic vehicles will join the assessment to make the planning more perfect.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b47fb29c6be0f07c367fff2529cad68e7d0e377e_1_690x286.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Social innovation drives regulatory innovation</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%B8%B6%E5%8B%95%E6%B3%95%E8%A6%8F%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Social innovation drives regulatory innovation" /><published>2018-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%B8%B6%E5%8B%95%E6%B3%95%E8%A6%8F%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%B8%B6%E5%8B%95%E6%B3%95%E8%A6%8F%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/">&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of my tenure, I met with former political commissar Feng Yan and handed over the business related to social enterprises. At that time, the teacher mentioned that if the regulations can be adjusted to allow non-profit organizations (NPOs) to set up corporate-type social enterprises, the cost of setting up social enterprises will be reduced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 Last October &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2017-10-31-%e7%a4%be%e6%9c%83%e4%bc%81%e6%a5%ad%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%80%e6%ac%a1%e5%b7%a1%e8%bf%b4%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0#s110683&quot;&gt;the first social enterprise action tour seminar&lt;/a&gt;, let me see the opportunity of the experiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that time, the Association of Taiwan Christian Good Shepherd Whole Person Care Association proposed that the company should establish a closed company in the name of a corporate legal person, and inject sufficient management and management expertise while fully utilizing &quot;one power.&quot; The design ensures the deduction of the business direction and the mission of the association.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🖇 In the past, there were few cases of “NPO financing companies”, and the establishment of corporate legal persons and companies belonged to different ministries. After the discussion, the Ministry of Economic Affairs of the Chinese Enterprise Office &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-01-05-%e7%a4%be%e5%9c%98%e6%b3%95%e4%ba%ba%e7%99%bc%e8%b5%b7%e6%88%96%e6%8a%95%e8%b3%87%e7%a4%be%e6%9c%83%e5%89%b5%e6%96%b0%e5%9e%8b%e9%96%89%e9%8e%96%e6%80%a7%e5%85%ac%e5%8f%b8%e5%af%a9%e6%a0%b8%e6%a9%9f%e5%88%b6%e8%a6%8f%e7%95%ab%e5%8d%94%e8%aa%bf%e6%9c%83&quot;&gt;actively coordinated&lt;/a&gt;, clarify the opinions of each unit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The People's Group Law stipulates that for the purpose of public welfare, social organizations must perform the tasks in the charter, and whether the establishment of the &quot;company&quot; is in conformity with the articles of association is the main consideration of the Ministry of the Interior.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Weifu Department believes that the purpose of the Good Shepherd Association is to provide social welfare services. After the establishment of a social enterprise, the business is more extensive. How to identify the competent authority requires more detailed discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Department of Economics of the Ministry of Economic Affairs reminded that non-profit organizations initiate registration of companies and require a letter of approval from the competent authority. In addition, the new company must meet the charity mission of the original legal person.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After many discussions, we have reviewed the review process of “initiating or investing in socially innovative lock-up companies”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;First, corporate legal persons must convene a general meeting to amend the articles of association and add The provisions of the company that allows the establishment of a company that meets the public welfare mission are allowed, and the new articles of association are submitted to the Ministry of the Interior for verification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of the Interior can decide whether to approve or not after replying to the opinions of the competent authorities of each business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After obtaining the letter of approval, the association can apply to the Department of Commerce of the Ministry of Economic Affairs for company establishment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚥 The “Regulations on the Development of Small and Medium-sized Enterprises” in the “Small and Medium-sized Enterprises Development Regulations” of the Ministry of Economic Affairs of the Ministry of Economic Affairs has a “General Law Sandbox” mechanism to create a safe space for friends who are investing in new ventures. In a certain period of time, you can experiment without legal constraints, and if you can, practice the law and keep up with the times. This case is a similar spirit, summed up the test rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Good Shepherd Association has followed the above procedure and has obtained a letter of approval to prepare an application for company establishment. I would like to thank all the friends of the ministries for their full assistance. As Lu Xun said: &quot;There is no way on the ground. If there are more people, it will become a road.&quot; I hope this is a starting point for the &quot;case experiment, establish the general rule&quot; and continue Innovate the way for social experimentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/001fc8eadae68d58b8ae817a22ac819d9bd89df3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">After many discussions, we took stock of the review process of “initiating or investing in socially innovative lock-up companies”.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/001fc8eadae68d58b8ae817a22ac819d9bd89df3.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Excessive tax rebate has a spectrum? Participants and the Ministry of Finance have a wide gap</title><link href="/en/blog/%E8%B6%85%E5%BE%B5%E9%80%80%E7%A8%85%E6%9C%89%E8%AD%9C-%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E8%88%87%E8%B2%A1%E6%94%BF%E9%83%A8%E8%AA%8D%E7%9F%A5%E5%B7%AE%E8%B7%9D%E5%A4%A7/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Excessive tax rebate has a spectrum? Participants and the Ministry of Finance have a wide gap" /><published>2018-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E8%B6%85%E5%BE%B5%E9%80%80%E7%A8%85%E6%9C%89%E8%AD%9C%3F%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E8%88%87%E8%B2%A1%E6%94%BF%E9%83%A8%E8%AA%8D%E7%9F%A5%E5%B7%AE%E8%B7%9D%E5%A4%A7</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E8%B6%85%E5%BE%B5%E9%80%80%E7%A8%85%E6%9C%89%E8%AD%9C-%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E8%88%87%E8%B2%A1%E6%94%BF%E9%83%A8%E8%AA%8D%E7%9F%A5%E5%B7%AE%E8%B7%9D%E5%A4%A7/">&lt;p&gt;On April 20th, the Ministry of Finance and the PDIS Group held the &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/78356a42-c8bb-45f2-a13f-5418fcf79cef&quot;&gt;Excessive Collection of Taxes - Return to the People&lt;/a&gt; at the Information Center of the Ministry of Finance &quot; Collaborative meeting in the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was reached by Jenny Wang on February 4, 2018, and reached the threshold of 5,000 on February 25th. After the vote of the Open Government Liaison Meeting, the Ministry of Finance and the PDIS team will hold it together. In the proposal, the proponent suggested that the Ministry of Finance should amend the law to distribute the excess tax collected on average to the taxpayer or to offset the tax payable for the next year. She believes that such a proposal can stimulate consumption and promote economic development. However, the Ministry of Finance does not believe that such a statement is reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;collaboration-meeting-attendees-are-not-familiar&quot;&gt;Collaboration meeting attendees are not familiar&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the day's meeting, Wu Jingqin, the teacher at the meeting, kept on raising procedural issues. He believed that the meeting did not submit information in advance about one week. He was given the feeling of &quot;raid&quot;; although he had a mental map at the meeting, he thought that the mind map was difficult to understand and should provide clerical information for pre-reading. In terms of numbers, he believes that there are more officials on the scene than the people. &quot;It seems that it is not going to listen to the public opinion.&quot; He worried that &quot;the people will have no voice&quot; and therefore protested many times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The host team, although explained, the choice of the participants is not based on the number of people, but the participants are expected to present multiple opinions as much as possible, so there are some restrictions on the number of people. However, Wu Jingqin did not accept the teacher and still thought that there were problems in the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-ministry-of-finance-explained-that-the-budget-is-only-an-estimate&quot;&gt;The Ministry of Finance explained that the budget is only an estimate&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the sponsor of the meeting was not present, it was customary to explain it by the Ministry of Finance. The Ministry of Finance pointed out that China's fiscal operation is to estimate the &quot;year-out&quot; of state expenditure at the beginning of the year and the &quot;year-end&quot; that may be received this year. However, this is only an estimate. At the end of the year, when calculating the actual value, there may be a gap with the estimate. If the actual annual income is less than the estimated annual income, it is called &quot;short-term&quot;. If the actual annual income is greater than the estimated annual income, it is called &quot;super-levy&quot;, but the super-levy and short-term sign are not related to the annual income, that is, even if the annual income is Over-levy, the annual income may also be much higher than the actual annual income, leading to the country's fiscal still deficit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/dfa25397e6f30e5036be470a2ec7557fe708ef14_1_690x461.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/40d7966e527f2d0d48406e50c53ab4064e2f9b3b_1_690x467.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/e/e31a97459b523fdf8b72368fe5373c3591433e4f_1_690x457.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The Ministry of Finance uses a slide to explain the basic knowledge of finance and taxation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Finance pointed out that the number of debt borrowings in the year will depend on the status of annual revenue and annual execution. As the past few years have exceeded, the rate of increase in government debt has continued to slow down. That is to say, since the actual annual output is higher than the actual annual income in recent years, how much money is over-levied, and the amount will be borrowed less in the year. In the follow-up explanation, Teacher Chen Guoliang added that if the people hope that these amounts will be refunded to the people, then the government will have to borrow extra money. I am afraid that there will be a situation of &quot;intergenerational plundering&quot;, that is, taking money from the pockets of future generations and returning taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/412c7d16f4c6eefe7d8424e3a6b77080b6d9770b_1_690x471.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The Ministry of Finance stated that the government still has public debt &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the proponent's argument that &quot;super levy should be refunded to the people&quot;, the Ministry of Finance explained that most of the countries that can benefit the people are financially well-received, and the annual income is greater than the annual income and there is a fiscal surplus, so the tax can be refunded. . Even if it is beneficial to the people or tax rebate to revitalize the economy, it must be included in the budget of the next year. After the review by the Legislative Yuan, the tax can be refunded. Moreover, the current status of the super-levy is different. If the consumption tax is excessive, it is difficult. Know who to return to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/a/a9eb41577b200135bd5fa2b01ed04d8f7de750ed_1_689x467.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Short-term situation of various tax items in the past four years &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the &quot;super-signal red envelope&quot; mentioned in the sponsor's copy, the Ministry of Finance explained that according to the fiscal revenue and expenditure division method, a certain proportion of the national tax revenue belongs to the local government. Therefore, before accounting for the central government's revenue, these taxes have been allocated to local governments in a fixed proportion. Only the distribution at the beginning and the middle of the year is allocated according to the estimated value. By the end of the year, since there are already the final accounts of the tax, they will be distributed according to the final accounts of the tax. If there is an over-levy in the year, the amount of the distribution will be higher. The media will be called the “extra red envelope”, but in fact these values ​​are the established distribution according to the law, and the tax amount after the distribution is counted in the central government. Years of entry. In the follow-up report, Mr. Chen Guoliang pointed out that there are many reasons for the over-levera. It is very likely that the Ministry of Finance has short-evaluated some values ​​in order to better meet the standards. He suggested that the Ministry of Finance should not use the term &quot;super-levy&quot; in the future. So as not to cause misunderstandings. He suggested that the Ministry of Finance should continue to review the reasons for the short-term assessment in the future, or use the interval to predict the annual revenue for the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/04c9a4f00a2b224680e61c5993f5ebb1e0344599_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Teacher Chen Guoliang explains the essence of Chaozheng &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the statement from the Ministry of Finance did not seem to let the participants of the meeting understand. Although the participants agreed that the definition of over-levy is the same as that of the Ministry of Finance, after the Ministry of Finance reports, the second party continues to question the continuation of the Ministry of Finance over the years is an illegal and inefficient performance, questioning the amount of over-levy may not be properly reviewed in the Legislative Yuan. The situation is illegally used. After the convergence of the host team, the views of the second party were clarified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-second-person-believes-that-the-super-levy-is-due-to-the-illegal-taxation-of-the-ministry-of-finance&quot;&gt;The second person believes that the super-levy is due to the illegal taxation of the Ministry of Finance&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second party believes that the excessive levy of the Ministry of Finance for many years is illegal and inefficient, and further they questioned It may be because the Ministry of Finance encourages taxpayers to tax illegally with tax incentives. These illegal taxes have led to the death of some people, and some industries have left. They believe that the amount of the super-levy is illegally used to issue tax incentives, and it is questioned that some tax incentives may become illegal gains. The proponents believe that Taiwan’s economy has been sluggish for years. It should be returned to the public with these over-levied funds to stimulate domestic demand and promote economic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/2/2f736ba1948c7f19fc45eab4ab4fc85f7d8fa53c_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Proposer explains the reason for the over-tax refund &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Finance responded that all taxes are taxed according to law. If there is a situation of illegal taxation, the government can use the relief channel, or it can be judged by the judge in the administrative court; tax incentives Some of them have already been answered in the previous proposal, and today I hope to focus on the discussion of the super-levy. As for promoting economic development, according to Chen’s report, if it is to promote economic development, expanding public spending may be more effective than returning to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two sides exchanged fires several times, and it is difficult for the collaborative meeting to enter the afternoon group discussion. Under the limited time, only the two sides can be sorted out (https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9J_kz3AqVk=/), provide a follow-up reference. At the end of the meeting, Lai Zhixiang of the Tang Feng Political Commissar Office stated that the results of the collaborative meeting will be referenced by the political commissar to the president and relevant heads of the relevant ministries in the government meeting as a reference for follow-up policy planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz3AqVk=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/277xxY5_t70&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;there-was-no-consensus-at-the-meeting-and-the-participants-still-insisted-on-the-original-view&quot;&gt;There was no consensus at the meeting, and the participants still insisted on the original view&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although there were many exchanges of fire between the two parties at the meeting, the presenters at the meeting still believed that the meeting had more explanations and focus, and thank you. The host team gathered their views. They believe that the officials of the Ministry of Finance can participate in the meeting is a sincere display, but perhaps there is a bigger conspiracy behind them to blind the officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second party believes that because of the previous election, it will be said that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cec.gov.tw/central/cms/bulletin/27242&quot;&gt;the referendum on over-tax refund will require a public hearing to clarify the issue&lt;/a&gt;, there may be people at the meeting who confuse the public hearing with this collaborative meeting. The second installers believe that the Ministry of Finance's explanations are still unclear. I still hope that the part of fiscal discipline can be improved. I also hope that Taiwan's economy can grow again through tax rebates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">The collaborative meeting discussed the issue of over-levy, but the gap between the proposal and the Ministry of Finance was wide. The two sides exchanged fires several times, and it was difficult for the collaborative meeting to enter the afternoon group discussion. Under limited time, the two sides could only be sorted out and provided for follow-up. reference.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/e/e31a97459b523fdf8b72368fe5373c3591433e4f_1_690x457.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Can unmarried women use artificial reproduction? Positive and negative sides have no consensus</title><link href="/en/blog/%E6%9C%AA%E5%A9%9A%E5%A5%B3%E5%AD%90%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E4%BD%BF%E7%94%A8%E4%BA%BA%E5%B7%A5%E7%94%9F%E6%AE%96-%E6%AD%A3%E5%8F%8D%E9%9B%99%E6%96%B9%E7%84%A1%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can unmarried women use artificial reproduction? Positive and negative sides have no consensus" /><published>2018-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E6%9C%AA%E5%A9%9A%E5%A5%B3%E5%AD%90%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E4%BD%BF%E7%94%A8%E4%BA%BA%E5%B7%A5%E7%94%9F%E6%AE%96%3F%E6%AD%A3%E5%8F%8D%E9%9B%99%E6%96%B9%E7%84%A1%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E6%9C%AA%E5%A9%9A%E5%A5%B3%E5%AD%90%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E4%BD%BF%E7%94%A8%E4%BA%BA%E5%B7%A5%E7%94%9F%E6%AE%96-%E6%AD%A3%E5%8F%8D%E9%9B%99%E6%96%B9%E7%84%A1%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98/">&lt;p&gt;On April 13, 2018, the PDIS team held the 30th Collaborative Meeting at the Airspace Society Innovation Center to discuss whether single women can have children through artificial reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was proposed by netizen Shu Kai Wu on the public network policy participation platform on January 4, 2018. &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/53479b9a-8cbb-4ea0-9f16-2294c97f24ac&quot;&gt;Open single women can legally perform &quot;artificial conception&quot; and &quot;test tube baby&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, after being linked by the netizens, and the open government contact person voted to vote, became the theme of the collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After several months of preparation, the meeting was held on April 13th at the Air China Social Innovation Center. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://hackmd.io/c/byg3w0-if/&quot;&gt;Issue Handbook&lt;/a&gt; was also produced for the participants to read beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;unmarried-people-do-not-apply-artificial-reproductive-discrimination-participants-changed-their-tone&quot;&gt;Unmarried people do not apply artificial reproductive discrimination? Participants changed their tone&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, the proponents reported that the UN human rights conventions guarantee the people’s reproductive rights. In addition to equal equality regardless of sexual orientation, this right should be treated the same whether it is married or not. Guarantee. At present, Taiwanese artificial reproduction can only be used by couples diagnosed as infertility, which is equivalent to discrimination against single women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/5/5a1cf8bdc150045df2c754c4022e445faf2b5383.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The sponsor proposes human rights and constitutional guarantees &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proponent pointed out that if the risks associated with artificial reproduction are used abroad, including excessive use of drugs, multi-embryo implantation, more money, and ultimately doubts that may lead to health and well-being, in order to protect those in need Rights, the government should open single women to use artificial reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, opponents believe that if artificial reproduction is to be used, in order to increase the chance of success, there may be a problem of tire reduction, which causes harm to life; religious belief does not allow masturbation to take fine. Opponents also believe that children born in a natural way of sexual behavior can have a happy family environment. The supporters believe that we should have multiple imaginations for the family. The families of modern society have become more and more diverse. We should understand the diverse nature of the family and give appropriate support. It is further pointed out that an important factor in the well-being of children is a stable family rather than a specific form of family structure. However, the opposition party believes that &quot;the law of nature represents the best interests of the child&quot;, and a family of one man and one woman is better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has also been a debate about the definition of unmarried women. The opposing party believes that the definition of unmarried woman should be &quot;lifelong celibacy&quot;, that is, &quot;everyone is prepared to be single, not married, and has no chance to have natural sexual behavior&quot;, but after some discussion, the legal definition of singles is still maintained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the reference materials, the two sides also had a confrontation. Among the materials prepared by the Ministry of Health and Welfare, the three materials that opposed the proposal were pointed out by the participating teachers to have serious problems. One of the studies also cited the study of rats, which might mislead the participants. The opponent said, &quot;You can't think that the mainstream opinion of 98 papers is wrong because there are two papers supporting different family types.&quot; After the moderator provided the information after the request, the opponent stated that the &quot;2 to 98&quot; argument is only a metaphor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opponents questioned the anonymous donation. When the child couldn't know his father, it might cause incest. He thought that &quot;sperm banks around the world are anonymous&quot;, but after a field of discussion, it is not true to clarify the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-meeting-focusing-supporting-measures-and-childrens-welfare&quot;&gt;Group Meeting Focusing Supporting Measures and Children's Welfare&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, the collaboration was led by consultant Zhang Fangrui and designer Lin Shuzhen, starting from the supporting measures of single women using artificial reproduction, trying to find Possible supporting measures and the trade-offs of participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/4/49e4e28b08cf172f38330f7ecece0e7331f2e0a8_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The first group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group pointed out that the biggest problem of artificial reproduction is that single parents are born, but is the single parent a problem or a phenomenon? In this regard, I hope that I can rely on professional research, such as tracking the development of children in single-parent families. However, the current research is almost all about heterosexual divorced and disharmonized families, so at present, it is produced for single woman reproductive work. The child problem has not yet found relevant research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it is only for single women to do economic or family support status review, I am afraid that it will become unfair to singles, and should be treated equally. All artificial genitals must check economic conditions and family background. In addition, a comprehensive social safety net should be constructed to support all care for single-parent families. If you are worried that your child will be discriminated against at school, you may need anti-discrimination education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to take into account the child's power to know the father, you can promote the anonymity and non-anonymous donation. If it is non-anonymous, you can design the system to let the child inquire after adulthood. It is suitable for single women and artificial reproduction. Couple. The second group will first find a consensus that artificial reproduction should exist, but it should be defined whether the state should take care of the reproductive rights of unmarried people. Then, the discussion is divided into two directions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One party believes that artificial reproduction should still conform to the laws of nature, and should be based on natural sexual intercourse, and the line does not need to be changed. However, the other side believes that although the law exists, because it is an unmarried woman, problems have arisen, such as discrimination against specific sexual orientation, marital status or economic ability, so it is hoped that the law can be promoted, such as the removal of the qualifications for marriage. During the discussion, some doctors at the meeting pointed out that there is indeed a need for unmarried artificial reproduction in Taiwan. Some families will require their girlfriends to get pregnant before they can get married. These people do need to use artificial reproduction in an unmarried situation. The second group also has another consensus. The well-being of children is important. Therefore, when evaluating single parents, you can refer to the current adoption system, find some institutions for evaluation, or consult counseling, social worker assistance, and so on. However, one party believes that the lack of male models for children's growth will have adverse effects. The other party believes that children do not have to have fathers. Instead, they have long-term supportive and good relationships, which is the key factor for children's growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/6/6e3c02e8e699a83a77c344dd21ca86e958c173aa_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The second group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of possible risks, the second group considers that the child needs to know his father. You can consider whether the donor chooses not to be anonymous, or refer to other countries to promote the situation, or refer to domestic NGOs such as “Gambling Family Rights Promotion”. Some manuals published by the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another risk and obstacle is that the process of repairing the law may take time and may require a special agency to supervise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kzqyefc=/&quot;&gt;These materials&lt;/a&gt; will be reported by the political commissar Tang Feng to the dean and the heads of relevant ministries at the government meeting every other week as a follow-up policy. Planning reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kzqyEfc=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5f2lxZqZjXE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-meeting-is-difficult-to-focus-on-the-sponsors-and-still-expects-the-issue-to-advance&quot;&gt;The meeting is difficult to focus on the sponsors and still expects the issue to advance&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer believes that the government can move forward after expecting the proposal, and it is expected that the government needs to listen to the positive and negative voices to make judgments, but this The meeting was not focused. She believes that how the host pulls back the focus is very important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the afternoon grouping, the sponsors thought that if the two groups talked about the same topic, it would be good, so that everyone can have more opportunities to speak. The proponent said that in the group meeting, the colleagues in the Ministry of the Interior will play the role of her, and indeed explain the connotation of the household registration law. The participants in the children’s position also have a professional support system that the children need is a strong support system. This is very good. Speaking. However, in fact, there are still those who speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the conference materials, the sponsors think that this conference is more like supplementing the information to the National Health Service, but some people's arguments do not give any justifications. Such remarks may be a waste of time for participants. However, the sponsor finally mentioned that through this meeting, she had increased some legal knowledge, but the opposing opinions still did not convince her. The proponents believe that the government should let the two sides understand each other, rather than having to follow up after the meeting. I hope that the government can make some progress on this issue and not let the folk resources be wasted.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">According to the sponsor's report, the UN Human Rights Covenant guarantees the people's reproductive rights. In addition to equal equality regardless of sexual orientation, this interest should be equally protected regardless of whether it is married or not. At present, Taiwanese artificial reproduction can only be used by couples diagnosed as infertility, which is equivalent to discrimination against single women. However, opponents believe that children born in a natural way of sexual behavior can have a happy family environment.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0202729ee380f76be840ca1d873218ac133bed9c.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Can the police be implemented? Collaborative meetings focus on improving the current system</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E8%AD%A6%E5%AF%9F%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E5%AF%A6%E7%8F%BE-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E7%8F%BE%E8%A1%8C%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can the police be implemented? Collaborative meetings focus on improving the current system" /><published>2018-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E8%AD%A6%E5%AF%9F%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E5%AF%A6%E7%8F%BE%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E7%8F%BE%E8%A1%8C%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E8%AD%A6%E5%AF%9F%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E5%AF%A6%E7%8F%BE-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E7%8F%BE%E8%A1%8C%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6/">&lt;p&gt;On March 31, 2018, the PDIS team held the 29th Collaborative Meeting at the Ministry of Finance Information Center to discuss the issue of the Mobile Police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case of the National Security Police was proposed by the netizen yc on the public network policy participation platform on November 25, 2017. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/7d9bdd7c-6b9a-4105-851d-8d75d74d2a8b&quot;&gt;No longer let the people who kill the roadside children go unpunished! Taiwan should follow the example of advanced countries. The police&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, after the netizens signed the election, and the open government contact person voted to vote, became the theme of the collaborative meeting .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, people's quality of life is guaranteed. Many people are also expecting animals to be treated humanely without being abused and killed by humans. In 1998, Taiwan Legislation passed the &lt;a href=&quot;https://law.moj.gov.tw/lawclass/lawall.aspx?pcode=m0060027&quot;&gt;Animal Protection Law&lt;/a&gt;, and we hope that through this law, we will respect animal life. With the concept of protecting animals. Many people also hope that Taiwan can set up an immobilised police to severely punish the crime of cruelty to animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;action-insurance-case-and-police-coordination&quot;&gt;Action Insurance Case and Police Coordination&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, according to Article 23 of the Animal Protection Law, local government insurance offices at all levels should set up full-time animal protection inspectors and select them. A compulsory animal protector to assist in animal protection inspections. Institutional, Taiwan adopts a model of cooperation between police and immobilities to handle cases of insurance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the public finds that the animal has been abused or treated improperly, you can call 110 to report it to the police station, or dial 0800-231-532 and hand it over to the insurance office. According to statistics, in 2017, the police received a total of 26 pieces of government insurance units from municipalities and counties (cities), and received 12,538.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the police receive a report from the public, if the situation is urgent, you can go to the scene to collect evidence, or go to the police with the mover to carry out the on-site search. Follow-up investigations are conducted by the insured, but if there is a need, they can go to the scene to inspect with the police. If it involves provisions relating to criminal liability, such as Article 25 of the Sports Protection Law, the police may also force force to intervene, or the prosecutor may apply for a search warrant to go to the site for a search. If a specific illegal act is found after the investigation, if the criminal law is violated, the prosecution agency may initiate the prosecution. If only the administrative law is violated, the mobile insurance department shall issue a penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help you understand this topic, the host team also prepared the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2pacx-1vruar-7rsrlvzjoflpdp4vlrmorr8srkf0o4-q89aag5jqvlteoxupbb5lq7mndwyshfq3m5qmivbfp/pub&quot;&gt;Issue Manual&lt;/a&gt; for Participants read the materials before the meeting to find out the current status of the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;morning-discussion-focus-issues-clarify&quot;&gt;Morning discussion focus issues clarify&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d68e0416977c378a8568dd9e86d112be15a77a2d_1_690x355.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Proposer report &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the day's meeting, the sponsor quoted &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tanews.org.tw/info/11227&quot;&gt;national security police system, which Taiwan is suitable for? &lt;/a&gt;, which explains the differences and implementation status of animal protection systems in each country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said that at present, the athletes are not trained in the search, and in the case of insufficient search, the situation of animal cruelty can not be conviction by the government; in addition, the current staff is insufficient, night, holiday Difficult to deal with immediately. The immobilities are not like the police, and they are almost incapable of intimidating effects on the general public. Therefore, in many cases, the insurance officer’s search and other treatments are easily ignored. Mr. Wu Zongxian, who attended the meeting, also pointed out that many of the motivators themselves are veterinarians. The effect of enforcement is very poor, and the lack of professionalism in the search for securities makes it impossible for the motivators to perform their business. Wu Zongxian believes that the police include a professional search, guidance, and even a symbol of authority. Wearing uniforms and guns is an effective administrative act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chief of the administrative team of the police department added that the police's search profession is also trained. At present, the police have also included the insurance case in the administrative rewards and punishments, but believe that the police have been generally overworked and do not wish to continue to increase. The amount of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The colleagues of the COA mentioned that the current training of the athletes will make up for the lack of professionalism, such as the profession of law, the profession of search, communication, dialogue and investigation. Come on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b6e305b6da41d376e54b21f5141865647d1aa6ab_1_690x356.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Participants and government colleagues work together to clarify the context of the issue &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The COA's colleagues also put forward figures further. Last year, there were nearly 700,000 inspections and active inspections including the cases of active insurance, and the number of complaints filed by the public was about 10,000 to 12,000. Pieces. However, there may be only 2,000 administrative punishments in these cases. The colleague explained that the public heard the screams of the dog next door and called the phone. This is a case, but is it actually a case and can it constitute an administrative penalty case? There is a large ratio that is not high. Further, the number and number of cases that were actually transferred to the local procuratorate for treatment, even by the courts, may be less than a dozen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the morning, the discussion focused on clarifying the issue and making the current system more complete. In the afternoon group meeting, they are divided into two groups to discuss how to make the relevant system of the motion insurance case more perfect. How can the motion-insurer, the police, and the prosecutor work together to complete this process, and how to enhance the awareness of the public Report abusive animal cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c752941b6d9cdfa6392b616c3b9f56383b26d24c_1_690x346.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Participants in group discussions &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-group-discussion-period-can-strengthen-the-cooperation-mechanism-between-the-police-and-the-police&quot;&gt;The group discussion period can strengthen the cooperation mechanism between the police and the police.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the group discussion, the first group pointed out that the athletes are not intimidating when they enforce the law, so they may have to be designed with dignity. Uniforms make him more like a policeman; in addition, he can also be equipped with some equipment, such as electric batons or batons. This part requires the cooperation of the competent authorities and the police department. In the case that the athletes cannot enter the house inspection, they hope to refer to the provisions of Article 19-1 of the Noise Prevention Law and the provisions related to the Law on Children and Children, so that the athletes can enter the residence on the basis of the basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of implementation, I hope that I can strengthen the training related to the law of forensic medicine, so that the athletes can have the ability to search and forensicate; the police should strengthen the knowledge of animal rescue. In the future, I hope that some police officers will train with the inspectors to make these police officers seed teachers. For the process, the athletes cannot receive the goods 24 hours a day, and may need to ask for assistance from the NGO or increase the number of posts in stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspectors, sometimes the police may not accept it, although the police said that the police will intervene in the &quot;crisis&quot;, but the concept is vague, suggesting that the &quot;crisis&quot; and &quot;emergency&quot; conditions can be defined. Can be included in the situation that has been repeatedly blocked by the parties, under these circumstances, the police should not dodge. For a long-term future, I hope to establish an immunization police mechanism in Taiwan. Finally, it is not easy to remember the number of mobile police calls. It is recommended that the image can be changed to 119 or 165.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second group of reports first confirmed the four aspects of the cognition: (1) There seems to be a lot of problems in the current cooperation mechanism between the police and the police, which may not be smooth or not implemented at all; (2) There may be many black numbers in the number of cases in which the insurance is completed; (3) the motion-insurer is not a 24-hour rotation. After the next shift, the athletes will create an empty window; (4) everyone is accompanying the police. The security personnel have high expectations and can increase the enforcement energy of the insured, so it may be a good solution to protect the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This set of discussion targets are serious cases of criminal insurance involving criminals. On this premise, the speed at which people dial 110 reports is the fastest. After 2015, because of the high-profile cases, it seems that there is no problem in the procedures for the joint attendance and the police to work together. However, at present, there are still problems in the black number of cases, after all, the animals will not take the initiative to report, and the public will not necessarily be willing to report the case, and the official will also accept the report before they can dispatch relevant actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the part of the mobile insurance office that does not answer the phone after work, the local government with abundant resources has 24 hours of rescue personnel. The animals can be initially rescued and disposed of, and the next day, the criminals will be transferred. The impact on the case will be less. At the same time, because the discussion targets are criminal security cases, the police are not at all, and the current system seems to be logical and smooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there may be some shortcomings in the promotion. In the internal part, the police may not realize that the insurance is also the scope of business. The police department deals with criminal cases and not all cases of insurance. Therefore, it is suggested that the COA can advocate that &quot;the abuse of animals is a criminal act&quot; and &quot;the crime should be called 110&quot;, so that the public can be aware that the case of insurance can be handled through the police. At present, the COA has also planned a series of follow-up awards, which should also be made known to the public. In the future, the COA and the Ministry of the Interior will continue to strengthen the government's colleagues. In addition to the Ministry of Agriculture's propaganda for the groups and the people who care about animal rights, the Ministry of Education can also play a role in strengthening life education. Part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0954a8f50b5aeeb3cf11f264b97b7fb4fa3f458f_1_690x349.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group report status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kzqybak=/&quot;&gt;conclusions&lt;/a&gt;, tang feng political commissar will send this information to the dean and relevant ministries at the government meeting on april 2 the head of the report is used as a reference for follow-up policy planning. conference-related &lt;a href=&quot;https://issuu.com/pdis.tw/stacks/347ec3a0ec4f471cb6f06a0091761c26&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-03-31-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e4%ba%8c%e5%8d%81%e4%b9%9d%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;verbatim&lt;/a&gt; will also Open on the Internet for the convenience of interested friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kzqyBak=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-proposer-is-expecting-to-have-follow-up-results&quot;&gt;The proposer is expecting to have follow-up results&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer said that he had played 1999 before this meeting. However, he believes that 1999 is more like a conduit for some people to vent immediately. However, even if there is more discussion in the collaborative meeting, I don't know if there will be any substantial consequences in the end. He mentioned that there was another case on Join, but when the department later went to the meeting, it felt like the case was &quot;destroyed.&quot; The sponsors were not very satisfied with the way we discussed today. She thought that the purpose of her proposal was to discuss the “moving police”, but the discussion focused on the “armed insured” and deviated from her original intention. The proposer hopes that there will be more time for the report, and it can also clarify the needs of the sponsors appropriately, and ask her to say more, rather than directly receiving the report of the ministry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sponsor still cares whether the case will have more follow-up results. Although the political committee reports to the president, it still depends on who is in the government and is willing to implement the discussion results. Wu Zongxian, a teacher at the meeting, pointed out that the issue involves &quot;moral issues&quot; and it is easy to arouse people's emotions. By clarifying the context, or evaluating it after the pilot, this type of policy can be better discussed in planning. Teacher Wu Zongxian believes that the follow-up of the collaborative meeting is a very important issue. Otherwise, it is a pity that it takes so much time and energy to prepare and meet, but there is no follow-up policy implementation. It is a pity.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On March 31, 2018, PDIS held a collaborative meeting at the Information Center of the Ministry of Finance to discuss Taiwan's animal protection system, clarify the difficulties in implementing the current animal protection policy in Taiwan, and the division of labor and security in the case of immobilities. the way.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/c/c752941b6d9cdfa6392b616c3b9f56383b26d24c_1_690x346.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Several small articles that allow the government to provide better digital services</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%B9%BE%E5%80%8B%E5%B0%8F%E6%A2%9D%E6%96%87-%E8%AE%93%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E6%8F%90%E4%BE%9B%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Several small articles that allow the government to provide better digital services" /><published>2018-03-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-03-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%B9%BE%E5%80%8B%E5%B0%8F%E6%A2%9D%E6%96%87,%E8%AE%93%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E6%8F%90%E4%BE%9B%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%B9%BE%E5%80%8B%E5%B0%8F%E6%A2%9D%E6%96%87-%E8%AE%93%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E6%8F%90%E4%BE%9B%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E6%9C%8D%E5%8B%99/">&lt;p&gt;In the past few years, under the initiative of the government and other athletes at the g0v zero hour, the Taiwan government’s open information has indeed taken a big step forward. But many people want to ask, can the government’s digital service be better? The government website has the opportunity to open Source, open up everyone to contribute? Can we use the better API to use the services provided by the government?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These problems, in fact, have been initially revised for the relevant administrative orders last year, making the Open Source and Open API of the government website possible; the problematic inter-departmental data connection problem is already being processed. . Beginning this year, the development of information services will gradually introduce a reference principle similar to the digital service of the UK GDS, so that the service is more in line with the needs of the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article will slowly tell you where we have corrected and what effect we can achieve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;common-application-interface-open-specification-standardizing-api-documentation&quot;&gt;Common application interface open specification, standardizing API documentation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to expand the efficiency of government information services and maintain the flexibility of API development, CDC refers to Open API Initiative (OAI) The API definition and description of the OpenAPI Specification (OAS) for the Advanced Application Programming Interface (API) translates the OAS 3.0 specification into Chinese and is released as the latest version of the [Common Application Interface]. Specification](https://theme.ndc.gov.tw/lawout/lawcontent.aspx?id=gl000270){:target=”_blank”}”, encourages agencies to participate in the introduction, hoping to use a consistent description method it provides api documentation that can be understood and used directly by humans and machines to greatly reduce the technical thresholds of data access, api adjustment and maintenance, making the connection of services more convenient. in order to make the apis have the characteristics of commonality, on july 13, 2006, the engineering council will amend the “information service purchasing contract model” by letter no. 10600218200 (https://www.pcc.gov.tw/cp.aspx?n=99e24daac84279e4){:target=”_blank”}”, understand that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The target version of the application interface development or enhancement should be based on the latest version of the National Development Council. The application interface is open to the specification, and the international common verification mechanism (suchastheOpenFoundationstandardoftheLinuxFoundation) is used as the basis for acceptance. “&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such a change, I hope that in the information development case of each agency, if the API provides external services, or develops the API for transmitting the data, it does not involve the API of the agility. Regardless of the authorization and access restrictions used by the API, the vendors are Instructions for OAS compliance are required and are described in the OAS standard. As a result, the API specifications of government websites are based on the use of international standards, which can effectively prevent their own situation and enhance opportunities for collaborative development with the international community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the Public Works Committee of the Executive Yuan also amended “&lt;a href=&quot;http://lawweb.pcc.gov.tw/lawcontent.aspx?id=fl000677&quot;&gt;Administrative Information Service Vendor Selection and Accounting Methods&lt;/a&gt;” Article 7, plus this amendment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The procurement software development service, the professional technical capabilities of the manufacturers specified in the second paragraph of the preceding paragraph, must be included before the zero cost or low cost, provided Common application interface development or integration capabilities that are freely accessible, usable, modified, and distributed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This fix is ​​intended to guide vendors to enhance and highlight their ability to provide common application interface development or integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After these articles opened the API for the API, Tang Feng did not force all government units to import OAS standard documents and APIs at the June 2017 meeting. The process, but with the announcement of the Information Supervisory Board, and the inclusion of the project review recommendations in the examination and examination, the 2017 plan for verification. We look forward to encouraging the ministry to adopt it through advocacy, providing practical standards and reducing costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;inventory-of-open-source-software-license-list-so-that-the-government-has-the-opportunity-to-open-the-website-source-code&quot;&gt;Inventory of open source software license list, so that the government has the opportunity to open the website source code&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The open source community has long expected the government to use the Open Source authorization method to allow the public to contribute their own strength, Improve the government website together. Beginning in 2016, the government also stated in the contract model of the information procurement standard:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When the manufacturer provides the agency services according to this contract, if the open source software is used, the authorized authority should use the scope of the open source software. And delivered to the agency in the form of the implementation file and the source code. The manufacturer shall deliver the open source software list (includingbutnotlimitedto:opensourceprojectname,sourceinformation,originalcopyrightclaim,disclaimer,opensourcelicensetermsandfulltext).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This correction allows manufacturers to take stock of the corresponding software when they make websites or provide information services for the government. After the software is authorized, the government can know which parts can be used by Open Source. Invite people to contribute and collaborate without worrying about the risk of infringement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;! &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2x/9/96d0477d55ad51fa59ef9929100ef78c238d0908_1_690x487.jpg&quot;&gt;The Administrative Commission’s Public Works Committee revised the “Information Service Purchasing Contract Model” Amendment Checklist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;unified-data-standards-for-future-inter-departmental-data-integration&quot;&gt;Unified data standards for future inter-departmental data integration&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because government websites or internal services are often commissioned by the respective ministries, internal data fields may not be consistent, resulting in Cross-section information is difficult to interface. Some friends expect that the government should implement data governance to unify the internal government’s data standards so that government departments can connect with each other through a unified API field, and people can better use government materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Development Council has now established the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ndc.gov.tw/content_list.aspx?n=b2a92523dcc12607&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Guidelines for the Establishment of the Field Data Standards Process&lt;/a&gt;”, starting from the fields of land administration, household administration, finance and taxation, commercial and industrial, highway supervision, labor insurance, health insurance, health and welfare, and financial, it is expected that the data standards for some of the data areas of these nine fields will be completed by August 2018. To facilitate cross-institutional data application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the longer term, “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ey.gov.tw/news_content.aspx?n=722606e55963357d&amp;amp;sms=a2fe4379891c538b&amp;amp;s=148acee4d1d5db4d&quot; target=&quot;_blank In the &quot;&gt;Digital National Innovation Economic Development Program&lt;/a&gt;” promotion measures, the handling measures of the spindle 3.3.1 were also used to specify “to create high-performance digital services with open standards and open source soft weights to create high-performance digital services.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;planning-government-digital-service-guidelines-to-make-software-development-more-in-line-with-user-needs&quot;&gt;Planning “Government Digital Service Guidelines” to make software development more in line with user needs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In software development, past governments often write their own requirements proposals by the ministry. Manufacturers can only make software according to this proposal, resulting in specifications. Not necessarily meet the needs. The draft &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/policies/detail/fd1415a8-a8fd-44bc-b5a4-6447918c9ab0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Government Digital Service Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; has been developed to include understanding of the use. 13 criteria, including cross-disciplinary cooperation mechanisms and planning multi-service pipelines, are expected to promote user-centered government digital services by introducing digital development directions similar to those of the United States, the United Kingdom, and Australia. As a reference for promoting digital services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These plans are all designed to improve the government’s ability to provide digital services. We look forward to gradually let the public authorities understand the key points of service design by encouraging the use of public service in the future, and take the spirit of data governance and information openness to take root in the government’s official culture.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">These small articles, from Open API and Open Source to service design, are expected to make the government's digital services more likely through the development of the system.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/96d0477d55ad51fa59ef9929100ef78c238d0908_1_690x487.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Mission is priceless</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%BF%E5%91%BD%E7%84%A1%E5%83%B9-%E5%95%86%E6%A9%9F%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Mission is priceless" /><published>2018-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%BF%E5%91%BD%E7%84%A1%E5%83%B9-%E5%95%86%E6%A9%9F%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%BF%E5%91%BD%E7%84%A1%E5%83%B9-%E5%95%86%E6%A9%9F%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90/">&lt;p&gt;The mission of social enterprises can be transformed into unlimited business opportunities? The practice from Fuxiyuan and 2021 social enterprises may be confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 Entering the Tanmei House in Taoyuan District of Kaohsiung, the room is full of plum fragrance. Mr. Gao, the peasant who guided us, said that these &quot;mei embryos&quot; can be processed into plum sauce and dried plums. These are the main products of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the Morakot disaster, in order to make the rebuilt Xiaolin Village really take root, Cai Songyu, the president of the Xiaolin Reconstruction and Development Association, began to look for the real estate industry. After stumbled upon the &quot;Old Plum Cream&quot; made by Xiao Linmei, he founded the 2021 social enterprise in the name of the local national roads 20 and 21, and worked hard to develop the &quot;Plum economy.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💰 &quot;When people say that they are giving him fish, it is better to teach him to fish, and we are making fish.&quot; Cai Songyu said that farmers sell green plums at an average of only 10 yuan per kilogram, and they signed contracts with Menon to guide and brew. Mei Technology buys the plum embryo at a price of 35 yuan per kilogram, and the profit directly returns to the farmers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future, 2021 will also develop leisure agriculture. The development of the “Meihao Economic Circle” is just around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other side of the Central Mountain Range is full of fragrance. Into the German small, who has been idle for more than ten years, Chen Rending, chairman of the Suntech Community Association, has a warm guide. He picks up the mint leaves and lemon grass. It turned out that they adopted a small German and transformed it into a vanilla laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As early as the Japanese Empire, Suntech Village was a herb planting base. Chen Rending, who resigned and returned to his hometown, decided to revive the community, invest in trials, and invite residents to work together. At present, the local herb planting area has reached seven hectares. The excellent environmental quality has also attracted many partners. One of them is the social enterprise “Fufuyuan”, which is the main social washing company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 Since the Fuxi Garden advertises zero chemical addition, the quality of the vanilla as raw material is sloppy. For this reason, CEO Zhan Ruhui traveled all over Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The land and water quality of Taitung is excellent. In addition, Suntech does not apply fertilizer and does not sprinkle pesticides. It is in line with her philosophy. Fuxiyuan is even directly produced and packaged locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎 Adhere to the concept and let Fuxiyuan gradually gain a foothold. Since last year, Fuxiyuan has entered the supermarket channel and entered the international market. Zhan Ruhui revealed that when she was in Canada, she had encountered a CSR purchase from a well-known company. When the other party understood the social enterprise concept of Fufuyuan, she said that she would not bargain and negotiate directly at the original price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2021 and the experience of Fuxiyuan let me see that the social mission is not only invaluable assets, but also contains high commercial value. How can social enterprises develop sustainably? The answer lies in the social enterprise itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7050491395513bb3e95c9ff4339c622ac891388d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;690&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">The mission of social enterprises can be transformed into unlimited business opportunities? The practice from Fuxiyuan and 2021 social enterprises may be confirmed.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7050491395513bb3e95c9ff4339c622ac891388d.jpg" /></entry></feed>